future.pk 2015-06-25

# Privacy Policy - Futurepk.com

**Privacy Policy**

Your privacy is valuable for future.pk and we don’t leave any stone unturned to protect your personal information.It’s against our policy to collect your personal information or ask you to give us your emails or cell phone number and if any user send us any email or provide us her/his cell number by the mean of comment or email we don’t approved that comment to protect their personal phone number and delete that comment at that time.

**What we collect**

  * We may collect the following information:
  * Total Number of Visitors
  * Total Number of Comments (Male,Female)
  * Demographic information such as Country,City Etc.

**What we do with the information we gather**

  * Internal record keeping.
  * We may use the information to improve our services
  * We may use the information to customize the website according to your interests.
  * We will never sell your information.

**Security**  
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

**Cookies**

**What are cookies?**

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer’s hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyze web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

**How we use cookies**

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

**Links to other websites**  
Our website may contain links to enable you to visit other websites of interest easily. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

For Contact!

Please Email US: arif-ca@live.com

Regards: Arif Hussain
